[Music]
hello everyone
and welcome to the ultimate health
advisor expo
this is a very unique event
that the max pooper team
has very carefully curated for you
and i am sure that you will find this
engaging
that you will find this relevant
and useful
today i wanted to share a number of
thoughts with you
my perspectives on what's going around
what's the opportunity that we see in
max lupa in health insurance
but before that
as you all know
we are living in unprecedented times
there are many industries
and many people
in our country who are going through
severe hardship
and i do want for us to take a moment
to acknowledge how fortunate we are
how fortunate you are
and how fortunate i am
that we are still in an industry that is
seeing growth
and is filled with opportunity
so with that i wanted to share my
thoughts with you on a number of topics
the first
and most important
is these times these covert times are
witnessing some very major shifts
some very big changes
and in my mind two stand out
the first is the change that's happening
with consumer behavior
now for those of us who've been involved
in health insurance
we've always known that health insurance
is about opportunity
we've always known that consumer
awareness of health insurance has been
growing over time
but what's changed now
indeed what's changed in the last few
weeks
has been the dramatic shift
of consumer behavior in terms of
decision making
for many of you who've been in sales
cycles
you know that
selling and health insurance has been
maybe days maybe weeks for customers to
make up their minds and to decide
but what we are seeing today is dramatic
customers are making up their mind in
minutes
if not in ours
so this is one very very big shift that
the health insurance market
in india is witnessing
the second one
and i have only one word to describe it
and that word is digital
again something that is not new
to our country
as as all of you know india has been
going digital
digital payments digital ways of doing
business
have been growing dramatically over the
last several years
but what's changed today again is a
dramatic shift in digital adoption if
you ask me there are only three states
for any business to be in today
the first state is the business has
already gone digital
the second
is the business is going digital
and the third
is if it's not one of these two the
business will die it's as dramatic as
that
if you look at your channel the agency
channel
your channel has gone digital
it has been going digital
whether it's
prospecting for new customers which
traditionally was a face-to-face process
today that process has gone social it
has gone digital
whether it's issuing policies
that is almost all digital as we speak
and indeed even when it comes to policy
servicing and claims
this is a this is going digital as well
so this is the second dramatic shift and
change that the current environment is
almost forced upon us
and as i look ahead i think these ways
of working
these shifts
are going to be permanent
the changes and habits
that the environment
has worked on all of us i think are
going to be permanent
and it's truly magnificent how
every business every channel in max pupa
has actually gone digital
and i'm very very confident that the
agency channel will ride this wave and
become even stronger in the times to
come the second topic i wanted to
address with every one of you is this
topic of opportunity
again an old one but given so much more
urgency in today's context
you know as as we have known and many of
us have been involved in insurance since
privatization way back in 2001.
health insurance has been growing at 20
25 every year
the really interesting and different
part different aspects to this industry
is the fact that even today after 20
years of privatization
we are still looking at the opportunity
to grow at 25 30
if you look at it on a state state by
state basis in india
the penetration of private health
insurance
measured by lives is no more than four
percent
so that's a staggering opportunity for
every one of us
to engage in and to make the best of now
what does this opportunity mean for you
for you as an advisor
i have one word
it is the opportunity for lifelong
income
in my opinion there is no financial
services product where you keep a
customer for life
so when we when you acquire a customer
relationship
when you sign up a customer
you sign up with the promise that you
will maintain a lifelong relationship
with that customer
and simply put that lifelong
relationship translates into a lifelong
annuity income for every one of you
so this is the really big opportunity
that continues to be there for you
my dear health insurance advisor
and lastly on this top on this topic of
opportunity i think and this is very
very important
uh you know we are
in a unique situation where in in doing
our business
in doing what we do for to make a living
we're also serving a very noble social
cause
i don't know how many of you know this
but the reality is that
every year and this number is probably
worse this year
more than 50 million indians become poor
because of inability to finance
unexpected health events
so you are actually not selling health
health insurance
you are actually taking health insurance
to customers
and so many millions and millions of
indians today are in dire need of this
product so frankly
the opportunity is is for you to run as
fast as you can and to help as many
indians as you can
now the last topic that i wanted to
cover with you
is why max pooper
you know as max pupa it is our our
mission
that we want to take health insurance to
millions and millions of indians and we
would very much
want to partner with you in our journey
so again why max pooper
let me just list a few reasons for you
first
is our strong brand
over the last decade or so we have built
what is arguably one of the finest
brands in health insurance
and in these times
in these uncertain times a strong brand
matters
it matters because people want safety
and security and people trust names
that they are used to and names that
they believe deliver consistent good
service
so reason number one strong brand
reason number two
is our track record of innovation when
it comes to product
we've recently launched a new product
reassure which is one more milestone in
our 10-year journey of taking to
customers
innovative and relevant products
so reason number two
products products that are innovative
and meet consumer needs
reason number three you know a strong
brand and great products don't matter
if at the end of the day we don't
fulfill our promises
have joined promises whatever you and we
commit to customers
and here i'd say that we have
a very strong culture of customer
centricity within the company
we
we are careful about the promises that
we make
because we are committed to making sure
that we honor every promise that we make
whether it's to our customer or to you
so backed by strong technology i think
our services and claims are unmatched in
the industry
last
and perhaps the most important
is i think max pooper has the finest
team
the finest teams
the finest team that brings to bear
expertise as well as experience
in the field of health insurance
so with that thank you my dear advisor i
wish you an engaging
health advisor expo
and we look forward to the journey with
you thank you
[Music]